overflowlegal.com 2008-10-16

# OverFlow Legal

## Privacy Policy

PRIVACY POLICY Uspeakwetype Technologies, LLC and any and all related entities including but not limited to the companies, products, and services found through the following URLS and any and all extension URLS: 

www.overflowlegal.com 

(hereinafter "Uspeakwetype Technologies") have adopted this Privacy Policy to notify you of its treatment of personal or personally identifiable information ("Personal Information") that may be collected when you are on a Uspeakwetype Technologies web site and when you use its services. This Privacy Policy does not apply to the practices of companies that Uspeakwetype Technologies does not own or control, or to individuals that are not under Uspeakwetype Technologies's actual control. 

Collection and Use of Personal Information. Uspeakwetype Technologies may collect Personal Information when you use the Uspeakwetype Technologies web site. The types of Personal Information you provide to Uspeakwetype Technologies on it web pages may include, name, address, phone number, e-mail address, and other information. Uspeakwetype Technologies is permitted to use your e-mail address, however obtained, to communicate with you and to update you on services and benefits and its trusted partners. By submitting an e-mail to Uspeakwetype Technologies or posting information on an Uspeakwetype Technologies website, you hereby agree that Uspeakwetype Technologies may contact you. Uspeakwetype Technologies may use this Personal Information to customize the content that you might see on the Uspeakwetype Technologies web site. 

Uspeakwetype Technologies may also collect data about usage and service operation that is not associated with specific personal identity. In particular, Uspeakwetype Technologies may log your IP address when you use the Uspeakwetype Technologies web pages or collect other information via cookies to evaluate how visitors use the Uspeakwetype Technologies web sites. 

User Choice. Uspeakwetype Technologies may use your e-mail address consistent with the above provisions. You are permitted and able to opt-out of communications from Uspeakwetype Technologies to you. 

Sharing and Disclosure of Personal Information. Uspeakwetype Technologies will not sell, rent, lease, or transfer your Personal Information to any individual, business, or government entity, unless to: (i) respond to duly authorized information requests of governmental authorities; (ii) comply with any law, regulation, subpoena, or court order; (iii) help prevent fraud or to enforce or protect the rights and properties of Uspeakwetype Technologies; (iv) to protect the personal safety of Uspeakwetype Technologies employees and third parties on Uspeakwetype Technologies property; or (v) unless it otherwise complies with this agreement Uspeakwetype Technologies will share your Personal Information with other entities only upon written request from you that Uspeakwetype Technologies share such information. 

User Account Access. Should Uspeakwetype Technologies assign you a username and password for access to any of its services, under no condition will Uspeakwetype Technologies share your user account information with another individual, business, or governmental entity, unless ordered to do so by a court of law pursuant to legal process. 

Protection of Personal Information. You are advised not to share unnecessary Personal Information, including any username and password with any other person. Unfortunately, no security system can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. Uspeakwetype Technologies uses commercially reasonable efforts to protect your Personal Information. 

Amendments. Uspeakwetype Technologies reserves the right to amend this Privacy Policy at any time. 

Contact. Should you have any questions regarding this Privacy Policy, you may contact Uspeakwetype Technologies directly by e-mailing contact (@) overflowlegal.com or write to us at the following address: Uspeakwetype Technologies 

810 Cottageview Drive, Unit G-20. Traverse City, MI 49684
